<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>curious george&#39;s tech playground</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on curious george&#39;s tech playground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:56:03 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gobuster Web Application Attack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/gobuster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:56:03 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/gobuster/</guid>
      <description>What is Gobuster? Gobuster is a Linux command line tool used to view all hidden pages of a website. Some websites will leave admin panels unprotected, leaving them vulnerable for us to attack. For this, will will be using a TryHackMe website called fakebank.com, so lets get into it. Note, this will not work if you use a general Linux Terminal, you must use the TryHackMe room.
Initiating the attack To begin the attack, we are going to open the Terminal and type in the follow command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:56:03 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/startup/</guid>
      <description>I have just recently created this blog, and I am testing out whether the post system works. I am unsure as to whether it will, but I hope it does. As to how I am making this blog, refer to below as I will explain exactly so. What to expect in this blog is a curious question, as I will do all the sorts. News, tutorials, how-tos, showcases, and generally me just doing a post on what I am doing at that moment in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:26:06 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Introduction root@curiousgeorge:~ $ cat info.txt My name is Sam, I&amp;rsquo;m from Australia and I am a big enthusiast in IT, and a nerd. I self-taught myself using Youtube videos, podcasts and lots, lots of Google searches. I especially enjoy the HAK5 podcasts, but there are numerous other ones I listen to aswell. I have no certifications in anything, no degrees, but I am still a reasonably well-knowledgable person in IT. My future is looking to be something as either an ethical hacker or pen-tester, but we&amp;rsquo;ll have to wait and see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
